CARMELITA WILEY

812 N 80th Terrace, Kansas City, KS 66112 \mid (H) 913-499-7149 \mid (C) 913-602-2004 \mid wiley.cdozuna.c87@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Customer Assistance worked with company systems such as Live support and diligently completed all assigned tasks, working overtime as needed Computed Data Reports Provided required weekly, monthly and quarterly reports listing sales figures and client track records. Customer Service Researched calmed and rapidly resolved client conflicts to prevent loss of key accounts. Product Sales cross-sold services at a rate of 30%, upgrading customers to different plans and product packages. Market Research o Interviewed clients via market research surveys to identify product issues and customer needs.

Skills

- Administrative background
- Skilled multi-tasker
- Highly motivated
- Advanced oral and written communication skills
- Types55 WPM
- Organized
- Customer service-oriented
- MS Office
- Advanced computer skills

Premiere Equity Assets - Laurel, MD

Strong organizational skillsActive listening skills
Seasoned in conflict resolution Top sales performer
Customer service expert Adaptive team
playerSharp problem solver Courteous demeanor
Energetic work attitude Telephone inquiries
specialist Telecommunication skills

Work History

Appointment Setter

07/2017 to Current

• My company purchases homes and properties from individuals to fix and re-sale. I call these people and inquire if they want to sale their property

• .

Appointment Coordinator

08/2017 to Current

Excel Lead Development - Cincinnati, OH

I set appointments for the company for different campaigns based on the clients needs they have me on a campaign calling on gas stations to see if they want to rebrand or build a new service station.

- Facilitated inter-departmental communication to effectively provide customer support.
- Met all customer call guidelines including service levels, handle time and productivity.

Customer Service Resolution Specialist

08/2014 to 07/2017

OnShore Marketing Solutions - Monterey, CA

I handled Newspaper subscriptions for different Newspaper companies all over the country. Handling Billing Issues, renewals not receiving papers, and various other issues to help customers. I also work on other projects for the company as well

Customer Service Representative

04/2008 to 08/2014

UPS Customer Center - Overland Park, KS

Answer incoming calls for customers tracking freight shipments, scheduling pickups, giving rate quotes for domestic and international areas.

- Handled all customer relations issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.
- Resolved all customer complaints in a professional manner while prioritizing customer satisfaction.

Customer Service Professional

01/1997 to 06/2008

Multi-service Corporation - Overland Park, KS

Duties include taking inbound calls for merchants authorizing credit cards over the phone. As well as filing invoices and inputting info in the computer.

- Reviewed field inspections and coordinated all insurance claim audits.
- Followed up on potentially fraudulent claims initiated by claims representatives.

Education

High School Diploma: 1993

Wyandotte High School - Kansas City, KS

Associate of Science: Secreterial/Business

1996

AVTS Kansas Area Technical School - Kansas City, KS

Secretarial/ Business Administration Vocational Certificate or Credential Clerical, Courses in Keyboarding & Document Processing, 10 Key, Filing(Alphabetically, Numeral, Geographic), Computer application software (WordPerfect 5 1, Windows-, Record Keeping, Data Entry

^{****}REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST*******